speeddial2.com 2017-04-26

# Speed dial 2 - the best New tab page extension for Google Chrome

* * *

  * This Privacy Policy sets out how we will treat the personal information which you provide to us while using the website located at [www.speeddial2.com](http://www.speeddial2.com/) (“ **Site** ”) and/or the services provided from it (“ **Services** ”). You are deemed to accept the terms of this Privacy Policy on your first use of the Site. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time and such changes shall be effective from the date and time the revised Privacy Policy is posted on the Site. 
  * To provide the Site and the Services, it is necessary for us to hold and process certain personal information. We take reasonable care in keeping this information secure and preventing any unauthorised access or unlawful use of it. All personal information is processed by us in accordance with data protection legislation. 
  * **What personal information do we collect from the people that visit website or app?**

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your email address or other details to help you with your experience.

  * **When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site or enter information on our site.

  * **How do we use your information?**
    * To personalize user's experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content in which you are most interested.
    * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
    * To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways: 

  * **How do we protect visitor information?**

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

  * **Do we use 'cookies'?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**We use cookies to:** • Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It won't affect the users experience that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.

  * **Third Party Disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. 

  * **Third party links**

We do not include or offer third party products or services on our website. 

  * If you do not want us to retain or use your personal information in any way, please withdraw your consent (i.e. “opt out”), by contacting us at [support@speeddial2.com](mailto:support@speeddial2.com). 
  * If you have any queries about this Privacy Policy or wish to resume receiving information which you may have previously opted-out of receiving, please contact us at [support@speeddial2.com](mailto:support@speeddial2.com).
